deobazaar.com 2019-06-24

# Buy more than 5000 deodorants online at DeoBazaar.com - lowest prices

The trust you place in us is valuable, so highest standards for secure transactions and information privacy are used at our end. By visiting DeoBazaar.com, you accept and consent to the terms and conditions of our privacy policy.

### **Note:**

Our privacy policy is subject to change without prior notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically.

## **Personal Information**

When you use our Website, we collect and store your personal information which is provided by you from time to time. This information helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at DeoBazaar.com. With our primary goal of providing a safe, efficient, smooth and customized experience, we use the information to assist ourselves in handling orders, deliver products and services, process payments, communicate with you about orders, products, services and promotional offers, update our records, and generally maintain your accounts with us, while displaying content such as customer reviews and recommend merchandize and/or services that might be of interest to you. We also use this information to improve our platform, prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our Website and enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf.

Below are the types of information we gather.

  * **In** **fo** **rmation Given By You:**  We receive and store any information you enter on our website or give us in any other way. Click here to see examples of what we collect. You can choose not to provide certain information but it might lead you to not be able to use certain features on the Website.
  * **Automatic Information:**  We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, we use "cookies" and obtain certain types of information when you access DeoBazaar.com or advertisements and other content served by or on behalf of DeoBazaar.com on other websites. We may also receive/store information about your location and your device. We may use this information for internal analysis and to provide you with location-based services, such as advertising, search results, and other personalized content.
  * **E-mail Communications:** To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open an e-mail from DeoBazaar.com. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers.
  * **Information From Other Sources:**  We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.

### **Examples of Information Collected**

### **Information Given By You**

This information is collected when you search, buy, participate in a contest or questionnaire or communicate with customer service. For example, you provide information when you: search for a product; place an order on DeoBazaar.com; provide information in Your Account/Profile; communicate with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise; complete a questionnaire or a contest entry form; provide reviews. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as: your name; address and phone number; credit card information; people to whom purchases have been shipped to; content of reviews and e-mails to us; the personal description of Your Profile; and financial information. 

### **Automatic Information**

Examples of the information we collect and analyze include: your IP address; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version; operating system and platform; purchase history, which we sometimes aggregate with similar information from other customers to create features such as Best Sellers; the full URL click stream to, through and from our Website (which may including date and/or time); cookie number; products you viewed or searched for; and any phone number used to call our customer service number. We may also use browser data such as cookies, Flash cookies, or similar data on certain parts of our Website for fraud prevention and other purposes. During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-hovers), and methods used to browse away from the page.

### **Information from Other Sources**

Examples of information we receive from other sources include: updated delivery and address information from our carriers or other third parties, which we use to correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily; account information, purchase or redemption information and page-view information from some merchants with which we operate co-branded businesses or for which we provide or take technical, fulfillment, advertising or other services; search term and search result information from some searches conducted through web search features; search results and links, including paid listings.

By using or continuing to use the site, you agree to our use of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, as may be amended from time to time by DeoBazaar.com in its discretion. You also agree and consent to us collecting, storing, processing, transferring and sharing information related to you with third parties or service providers for the purposes as set out in this Privacy Policy.

We may be required to share the aforesaid information with government authorities and agencies for the purposes of verification of identity or for prevention, detection or investigation, including of cyber incidents, prosecution and punishment of offences. You agree and consent for DeoBazaar.com to disclose your information, if so required, under applicable law. 

## **Cookies**

We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of the Website to help analyze our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. Cookies are small digital signature files stored by your web browser that allow your preferences to be recorded when visiting the Website; to track your return visits to the Website by and not limited to third-party advertising companies. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a cookie. We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on the Website and you may be required to re-enter your password more frequently during a session. 

Additionally, you may encounter cookies or other similar devices on certain pages of the Website that are placed by third parties. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties.

## **Sharing of Personal Information**

Information shared by you or obtained otherwise (as mentioned above) is an integral part of our corporation and we are not in the business of selling it to others. DeoBazaar.com shares customer information only as described below. 

  * **Affiliated Businesses:** We may share personal information with our other corporate entities and affiliates. These entities and affiliates may market to you as a result of such sharing unless you explicitly opt-out. 
  * **Third Party Service Providers:**  We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples might include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analysing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. Further, they must process the personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and as permitted by applicable law. We do not disclose your personal information to third parties for their marketing and advertising purposes without your explicit consent. 
  * **Protection of DeoBazaar.com and Others:** We may release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with applicable law; enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions and other agreements; or protect the rights, property or safety of DeoBazaar.com, our users or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies, organizations, third party right owners to respond to claims of any content violating their rights, government or regulatory authorities for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in a way that is contrary to the commitments made in this Privacy Policy. 
  * **With your consent:**  Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information. 

We and our affiliates will share / sell some or all of your personal information with another business entity should we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity, or re-organization, amalgamation, restructuring of business. Should such a transaction occur that other business entity (or the new combined entity) will be required to follow this Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information. ****

## **Information Security**

Our Website has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the information you input in addition to maintaining security of your information as per the International Standard IS/ISO/IEC 27001.

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage, and disclosure, of personal information. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you.

## **Notices and Revisions**

If you have any concern about privacy or grievances at DeoBazaar.com, please [contact us](https://www.deobazaar.com/Contact-Us.html "Help Desk No") with a thorough description and we will try to resolve the issue for you.

Our business changes constantly and so do our Privacy Policy, Terms and Conditions. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, but you should check our Website frequently to keep yourself up to date with the recent changes.

Unless stated otherwise, out current Privacy Policy applies to all information we have about you and Your Account. We stand behind the promises we make, and assure that we will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.
